[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the communities formed by rabbits living together?", "correct_answer": "Warrens", "incorrect_answers": ["Herds", "Schools", "Flocks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "North Carolina has been well represented on the American Idol TV series Which contestant from the state became Americas Idol in 2004?", "correct_answer": "Fantasia Barrino", "incorrect_answers": ["Kerrier Ann Pickler", "Clay Aiken", "Taylor Hicks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name for baby sharks?", "correct_answer": "pups", "incorrect_answers": ["calves", "pecks", "cubs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the tomato plant does not contain Solanine, a poison toxic to humans and animals?", "correct_answer": "Ripe fruit", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Leaves", "Unripe fruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following films was not directed by Mel Brooks?", "correct_answer": "The Jerk", "incorrect_answers": ["Robin Hood: Men in Tights", "High Anxiety", "Silent Movie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the presidential residence called The Blue House?", "correct_answer": "South Korea", "incorrect_answers": ["Argentina", "Greece", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This shark is considered a filter- feeder. Its diet consists mainly of plankton, krill, and macro-algae.", "correct_answer": "whale shark", "incorrect_answers": ["bull shark", "great white shark", "pygmy shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hippos secrete a red substance known as blood sweat that protects them from the sun.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Immanuel Kant criticized Emanuel Swedenborg and termed him a \u201cspook hunter\u201d.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of what type of birds is forbidden by Jewish dietary laws?", "correct_answer": "Birds of prey", "incorrect_answers": ["Mute birds", "Black birds", "Flightless birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how long does it take a fingernail to grow from the base to the tip?", "correct_answer": "6 months", "incorrect_answers": ["6 days", "6 weeks", "2 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are two main sources of salt - sea water and rock salt.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]